bbsoftware.co.uk 2008-06-23

# Blueberry Software - Privacy Policy

Blueberry has produced this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our commitment to respecting your privacy and personal information. The policy below outlines the information that we may collect and how we may use it. 

**How we gather and use Personal Information**  
Blueberry Consultants will not collect any personally-identifiable information about you (e.g. name, address, e-mail address, credit card number, expiration date) without you agreeing to provide it to us on a voluntary basis. We will collect information when you sign up for any of our shareware, demoware or general newsletter services to use to send the information you have requested or other news items that you may be interested in. We may store and process this information to better understand your needs and to personalise your experience as a Blueberry Consultants customer. We may also monitor user traffic patterns and use of our site with this information to help improve the design, layout and content. 

**Our use of cookies**  
We do use cookies - but only if you give us permission to do so. Like many websites, we use text files known as 'cookies' to gather information, which helps us to provide useful features to our customers. We can also use these cookies to save your password so you don't have to re-enter it each time you visit our site, and to record how often you visit the site and the areas you visit within it, but only if you have selected the option agreeing to our doing this. Cookies themselves do not personally identify users, although they can identify a user's computer. You can set your browser to refuse cookies if you wish to, however, you may not be able to take full advantage of our web site if you do. 

**Will Blueberry sell my personal information to other companies?**  
We may pass your email address on to authorised resellers in your region. 

Other than authorised resellers, Blueberry Consultants will not give or sell your personal information to any outside organisation for that organisation's own use without your consent. We may on occasion, team up with other businesses to enable us to provide special services to you during which we will use this information but you will be given every opportunity to opt out of these before hand.

Blueberry Consultants may disclose personal information if required to do so by law or in the good-faith belief that such action is necessary to a) conform with the law; b) protect and defend the rights or property of Blueberry, the site or the users of Blueberry sites, and c) act in circumstances where it is necessary to protect the personal safety of users of Blueberry, our sites or our users or other. 

**Financial Information**  
We use financial information collected from you only to invoice you for products and services you have bought via the site should this be necessary. At this time, unique identifiers may be collected to verify your identify. 

**Updating or changing information we collect**  
To review or edit the information in our database, login to the website and clck the 'Edit Profile' button in the Welcome box on the right hand side of any page. 

**Security**  
This site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control and personal information collected by us is stored in secure operating environments that are not available to the public.
